https://www.meredith-zinner-photography.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how Meredith Zinner Photography or ‘we’ use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
What information do we collect?
Why we need collect data?
How long do we keep your data?
Marketing
What are your rights?
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
What information do we collect?
We collect information about you when you fill in a contact form or email us directly, including your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, company name. We also collect information when you voluntarily comment on our blog posts or provide feedback.
Website usage information is collected using cookies. The information we collect about you includes; your geographic location, your name, internet browser, internet service provider, operating system, device manufacturer and model.
Why do we collect data?
We collect information about you to; fulfill your request e.g. if you fill out a ‘request a callback’ form we use this information to contact you directly, process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about other products, services, and information we think may be of interest to you. We may use your contact information to advertise our service to you on third-party websites such as Facebook, Twitter and Google advertising partners. We may also contact you directly to follow up on the service and user experience we provide. We use your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to our website. If Meredith Zinner Photography is ever sold to another company your contact information will be passed on to this new party.
We will take cautionary measure to ensure we do not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee the above services to you.
How long do we keep your data?
If Meredith Zinner Photography provides any paid for services to you, we keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 7 years. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.
Marketing
We would like to send you updates and information about products and services of ours which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other parties. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes please click here.
What are your rights?
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address.
Email: info@mzphotography.com
Address: 285 5th Avenue #422, Brooklyn, NY 11215
You may also request that we correct or delete your personal information.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. If you visit other websites, be sure to read their own privacy policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
Any updates to our privacy policy will be posted on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
Email: info@mzphotography.com
Address: 285 5th Avenue #422, Brooklyn, NY 11215
